Guide to the Records of the New York University Photo Bureau RG.7.2.2
New York University Archives
- Negatives, 1952-2007
  - Negatives 96-385 A-C to 96-422 M-O, 1997 (Box 478c)
  - Negatives 96-423 A-C to 96-474 A, 1997 (Box 478d)
  - Negatives 96-475 A-C to 96-518 D-E, 1997 (Box 478e)
  - Negatives 96-520 A-C to 96-555 G, 1997 (Box 478f)
  - Negatives 96-556 A-C to 96-595 D-E, 1997 (Box 478g)
  - Negatives 96-596 A-C to 96-630 A-B, 1997 (Box 479)
  - Negatives 96-631 A-B to 96-657 A, 1997 (Box 480)
  - Negatives 96-658 A to 97-027 A, 1997 (Box 481)
  - Negatives 97-021 A-B to 97-050 D-E, 1997 (Box 482)
  - Negatives 97-051 A-C to 97-101 D, 1997 (Box 483)
  - Negatives 97-102 A to 97-144 A-C, 1997 (Box 484)
  - Negatives 97-145 A-B to 97-199 A-C, 1997 (Box 485)
  - Negatives 97-201 A-C to 97-245 D, 1997-1998 (Box 486)
  - Negatives 97-246 A-C to 97-283 S-T, 1998 (Box 487)
  - Negatives 97-284 A-B to 97-331 A-C, 1998 (Box 488)
  - Negatives 97-332 A-C to 97-366 A-C, 1998 (Box 489)
  - Negatives 97-367 A-B to 97-415 A-C, 1998 (Box 490)
  - Negatives 97-416 A-C to 97-453 G, 1998 (Box 491)
  - Negatives 97-454 A-C to 97-492 G, 1998 (Box 492)
  - Negatives 97-495 A-C to 97-525 A-B, 1998 (Box 493)
  - Negatives 97-526 A-C to 97-565 G-H, 1998 (Box 494)
  - Negatives 97-567 A-C to 97-586 P, 1998 (Box 495)
  - Negatives 98-001 A-C to 98-038 G-I, 1998 (Box 496)
  - Negatives 98-039 A-B to 98-072 G-I, 1998 (Box 497)
  - Negatives 98-075 A-C to 98-125 D-E, 1998 (Box 498)
  - Negatives 98-126 A-C to 98-171 D, 1998 (Box 499)
  - Negatives 98-156 A-B to 98-202 G, 1998 (Box 500)
  - Negatives 98-203 A-C to 98-243 J-L, 1998-1999 (Box 501)
  - Negatives 98-244 A-C to 98-288 A-C, 1999 (Box 502)
  - Negatives 98-291 A-B to 98-333 A-C, 1999 (Box 503)
  - Negatives 98-334 A-B to 98-384 D, 1999 (Box 504)
  - Negatives 98-385 A-C to 98-417 D, 1999 (Box 505)
  - Negatives 98-418 A to 98-456 D-E, 1999 (Box 506)
  - Negatives 98-457 A-C to 98-494 G, 1999 (Box 507)
  - Negatives 98-495 A-C to 98-520 A, 1999 (Box 508)
  - Negatives 98-522 A-C to 98-562 G, 1999 (Box 509)
  - Negatives 98-563 A-C to 98-604 S-T, 1999 (Box 510)
  - Negatives 98-608 A-B to 98-635 A-C, 1999 (Box 511)
  - Negatives 99-001 A-B to 99-032 P-R, 1999 (Box 512)
  - Negatives 99-034 A-C to 99-080 D-E, 1999 (Box 513)
  - Negatives 99-081 A-C to 99-130 A-C, 1999 (Box 514)
  - Negatives 99-131 A-B to 99-179 G, 1999 (Box 515)
  - Negatives 99-180 A-C to 99-219 A-B, 1999-2000 (Box 516)
  - Negatives 99-220 A-B to 99-247 M, 2000 (Box 517)
  - Negatives 99-249 A-C to 99-269 A, 2000 (Box 518)
  - Negatives 99-270 A-C to 99-288 A-C, 2000 (Box 519)
  - Negatives 99-289 A-B to 99-304 A-C, 2000 (Box 520)
  - Negatives 99-305 A-C to 99-346 A, 2000 (Box 521)
  - Negatives 99-347 A-C to 99-371 A-C, 2000 (Box 522)
  - Negatives 99-380 A-C to 99-414 D-F, 2000 (Box 523)
  - Negatives 99-415 A-C to 99-449 A-B, 2000 (Box 524)
  - Negatives 99-450 A-C to 99-468 D-F, 2000 (Box 525)
  - Negatives 99-468 G-I to 99-494 A, 2000 (Box 526)
  - Negatives 99-495 A-B to 99-520 M-O, 2000 (Box 527)
  - Negatives 99-520 P-R to 99-538 A-C, 2000 (Box 528)
  - Negatives 99-538 D-E to 99-560 A-B, 2000 (Box 529)
  - Negatives 00-002 A-C to 00-041 D-E, 2000 (Box 530)
  - Negatives 00-044 A-C to 00-078 D-F, 2000 (Box 531)
  - Negatives 00-078 G-I to 00-100 A, 2000 (Box 532)
  - Negatives 00-101 A to 00-130 A-C, 2000 (Box 533)
  - Negatives 00-131 A-C to 00-165 D, 2000 (Box 534)
  - Negatives 00-166 A-C to 00-216 A, 2000-2001 (Box 535)
  - Negatives 00-218 A-C to 00-251 V-X, 2001 (Box 536)
  - Negatives 00-253 A-C to 00-294 D, 2001 (Box 537)
  - Negatives 00-295 A-C to 00-337 J-L, 2001 (Box 538)
  - Negatives 00-337 M-O to 00-362 D-E, 2001 (Box 539)
  - Negatives 00-364 A-C to 00-404 A-C, 2001 (Box 540)
  - Negatives 00-404 D-F to 00-437 A-C, 2001 (Box 541)
  - Negatives 00-437 D to 00-475 V-X, 2001 (Box 542)
  - Negatives 00-475 Y-AA to 00-495 D-F, 2001 (Box 543)
  - Negatives 00-495 G-I to 00-511 M-O, 2001 (Box 544)
  - Negatives 00-511 P-R to 00-554 D-F, 2001 (Box 545)
  - Negatives 00-554 G-I to 00-571 TT-VV, 2000-2001 (Box 546)
  - Negatives 00-571 WW-YY to 00-611 A-B, 2001 (Box 547)
  - Negatives 00-612 A-C to 01-004 A, 2001-2002 (Box 548)
  - Negatives 01-005 A-C to 01-053 A-B, 2002 (Box 549)
  - Negatives 01-054 A-C to 01-088 D-F, 2002 (Box 550)
  - Negatives 01-088 G-H to 01-115 D-F, 2002 (Box 551)
  - Negatives 01-115 G-I to 01-138 A-C, 2002 (Box 552)
  - Negatives 01-139 A-C to 01-181 A, 2002 (Box 553)
  - Negatives 01-182 A-C to 01-221 D, 2002 (Box 554)
  - Negatives 01-222 A to 01-266 J-K, 2002 (Box 555)
  - Negatives 01-268 A to 01-676 D-F, 2001-2002 (Box 556)
  - Negatives 01-677 A-B to 01-717 A-B, 2001 (Box 557)
  - Negatives 01-718 A-B to 01-762 D-F, 2001 (Box 558)
  - Negatives 01-763 A-B to 01-806 D, 2001 (Box 559)
  - Negatives 01-807 A-C to 01-828 A-C, 2002 (Box 560)
  - Negatives 01-828 D-F to 01-856 S-U, 2002 (Box 561)
  - Negatives 01-856 V-X to 01-898 A-C, 2002 (Box 562)
  - Negatives 01-899 A-C to 01-942 G, 2002 (Box 563)
  - Negatives 01-943 A to 01-986 D-E, 2002 (Box 564)
  - Negatives 01-987 A-C to 02-007 G-H, 2002 (Box 565)
  - Negatives 02-008 A-B to 02-045 V, 2002 (Box 566)
  - Negatives 02-048 A to 02-100 D-E, 2002 (Box 567)
  - Negatives 02-151 A-C to 02-195 A-C, 2002 (Box 568a)
  - Negatives 02-101 A-C to 02-148 G-H, 2002 (Box 568b)
  - Negatives 02-196 A-C to 02-234 D-E, 2002-2003 (Box 569)
  - Negatives 02-235 A-C to 02-290 A-C, 2003 (Box 570)
  - Negatives 02-291 A-C to 02-328 A, 2003 (Box 571)
  - Negatives 02-329 A to 02-358 J, 2003 (Box 572)
  - Negatives 02-360 A-C to 02-390 D-F, 2003 (Box 573)
  - Negatives 02-391 A-B to 02-426 A-B, 2003 (Box 574)
  - Negatives 02-427 A-C to 02-479 D-E, 2003 (Box 575)
  - Negatives 02-480 A-C to 02-501 G-I, 2003 (Box 576)
  - Negatives 02-503 A-C to 02-588 A-B, 2003 (Box 577)
  - Negatives 03-004 A to 03-074 D-F, 2003 (Box 578)
  - Negatives 03-075 A to 03-136 A-C, 2003 (Box 579)
  - Negatives 03-140 A-C to 03-241 P-Q, 2003 (Box 580)
  - Negatives 03-242 A-C to 03-303 A-C, 2003-2004 (Box 581)
  - Negatives 03-306 A to 03-339 D-E, 2004 (Box 582)
  - Negatives 03-340 A-C to 03-382 V, 2004 (Box 583)
  - Negatives 03-387 A to 03-464 HH, 2004 (Box 584)
  - Negatives 03-466 A to 03-534 A-C, 2004 (Box 585)
  - Negatives 03-536 A-B to 03-586 D-F, 2004 (Box 586)
  - Negatives 03-589 A-C to 03-637 A-B, 2004 (Box 587)
  - Negatives 04-002 A to 04-019 M-O, 2004-2005 (Box 588)
  - Negatives 04-021 A-C to 04-082 A-C, 2004-2005 (Box 589)
  - Negatives 04-082 D-E to 04-199 G-H, 2004 (Box 590)
  - Negatives 04-206 A-C to 04-266 X-Z, 2004-2005 (Box 591)
  - Negatives 04-266 AA-CC to 04-399 G-H, 2005 (Box 592)
  - Negatives 04-407 A-C to 04-556 A-B, 2005 (Box 593)
  - Negatives 04-561 A-B to 04-649 A-C, 2005 (Box 594)
  - Negatives 04-652 A-C to 04-716 A-B, 2005 (Box 595)
  - Negatives 05-015 A to 05-164 D, 2005 (Box 596)
  - Negatives 05-179 A-C to 05-397 D, 2005-2006 (Box 597)
  - Negatives 05-405 A-C to 05-679 D-F, 2006 (Box 598)
  - Negatives 06-039 A-B to 06-309, 2006-2007 (Box 599)
  - DELETE Unprocessed Negatives (Box 478b, Box 478c, Box 478d, Box 478e, Box 478f, Box 478g)
- Commencement slides, 2002 (Box Shared University Archives 049, Folder 1)